JIHEE MOON

QLD 4215 0423692155 mj824m@gmail.com https://github.com/jiheemoon linkedin.com/in/jihee-moon-450737178

Professional Summary

Analytical Java Developer with 3+ years of experience handling popular web languages and Javascript to develop and implement applications based on customers' needs. Exceptional technical skills in coding and software development. Forward-thinking professional talented at developing creative solutions for complex technical problems.

Work History

Java Developer Apr 2019 - May 2022

Haesoldata Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea

Collaborated in a team-based, Agile environment to accomplish objectives by deadlines.

Participated in requirements gathering and design development meetings.

Reviewed code and debugged errors to improve performance.

Wrote, modified and maintained software documentation and specifications.

E-learning system Maintenance	Feb 2021 - Feb 2022
Development and Establishment of CRM	May 2020 - JAN 2021
Development of AD Connector (SSO)	Apr 2020 - May 2020
Development and Establishment of Internal Accounting System	Apr 2019 - Apr 2020

Education

Academy in Java Framework DeveloperTraining Course Oct 2018 - Mar 2019

KH Information Education Center, Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science: Smart IT Mar 2015 - Feb 2019

Doowon Technical University Paju, Gyeonggi Province, Korea

Skills

Linux Environments Spring DAO Software Deployment JavaScript Security Planning Web Programming Critical Thinking RDMS Development and SQL Spring MVC Organization and Time Management Apache Maven Performance Evaluation and Optimization User Interface (UI) Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) SOAP and Restful Web Services Source and Version Control: Git, GitHub

Programming Languages: Java, Python

Accomplishments

Apache Tomcat

Doowon Entrepreneurship Competition (Excellence Award) Jun 2018

Anti freezing system using ac current

source link: https://github.com/jiheemoon/DonPaBangz

Certifications

Industrial Engineer Information Processing Mar 2019

Human Resources Development Service of Korea

Linux Master Grade II Dec 2018

KAIT

Additional Information

Working holiday VISA (unrestricted working rights)	JUL 2023
Driver License (Manual)	Feb 2015